A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, President, Karen Davis papers, SG 2 FA1127
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Correspondence, 3; 7.38 Cubic Feet
  - Karen Davis Correspondence - M-O, 1997-1998 (Box 47, Folder 410)
  - Karen Davis Correspondence - P-Q, 1994-1998 (Box 47, Folder 411)
  - Karen Davis Correspondence - R-S, 1996-1998 (Box 48, Folder 412)
  - Karen Davis Correspondence - T-V, 1994-1998 (Box 48, Folder 413)
  - Karen Davis Correspondence - W-Z, 1993-1999 (Box 48, Folder 414)
  - Karen Davis Correspondence 1999 - A-B (Box 48, Folder 415)
  - Karen Davis Correspondence 1999 - C-E (Box 48, Folder 416)
  - Karen Davis Correspondence 1999 - F-Z (Box 49, Folder 417-424)
  - Board Correspondence - Ashe Resolution, 1994-1998 (Box 50, Folder 425)
  - Board Correspondence - Arhur Ashe, 1991-1994 (Box 50, Folder 426)
  - Board Correspondence - Hubert S. Aldrich, 1971-1994 (Box 50, Folder 427-428)
  - Board Correspondence - Malcolm P. Aldrich Resolution, 1987 (Box 50, Folder 429)
  - Board Correspondence - Malcolm P. Aldrich, 1968-1992 (Box 50, Folder 430-431)
  - Board Correspondence - Harriet B. Beilin, 1979-2000 (Box 51, Folder 432)
  - Board Correspondence - George Packer Berry, 1971-1986 (Box 51, Folder 433)
  - Board Correspondence - Rodger M. Blough, 1971-1985 (Box 51, Folder 434)
  - Board Correspondence - Lewis Branscombe, 1966-1997 (Box 51, Folder 435)
  - Board Correspondence - Carleton B. Chapman, 1975-1997 (Box 51, Folder 436-437)
  - Board Correspondence - Carleton B. Chapman, 1974-1982 (Box 52, Folder 438)
  - Board Correspondence - Frederick M. Eaton, 1971-1984 (Box 52, Folder 439)
  - Board Correspondence - Robert Ebert, 1995-1996 (Box 52, Folder 440)
  - Board Correspondence - C. Simms Farr, 1980-1998 (Box 52, Folder 441-442)
  - Board Correspondence - C. Simms Farr, 1975-1980 (Box 53, Folder 443)
  - Board Correspondence - John A. Gifford, 1975-1989 (Box 53, Folder 444)
  - Board Correspondence - Robert J. Glaser, 1969-1999 (Box 53, Folder 445-447)
  - Board Correspondence - R. L. Ireland, III, 1977-1999 (Box 54, Folder 448)
  - Board Correspondence - Margaret E. Mahoney, 1980-1999 (Box 54, Folder 449)
  - Board Correspondence - William H. Moore, 1970-1994 (Box 54, Folder 450)
  - Board Correspondence - Quigg Newton, 1974-1998 (Box 54, Folder 451)
  - Board Correspondence - Roswell B. Perkins, 1974-1998 (Box 54, Folder 452-453)
  - Board Correspondence - Calvin H. Plimpton, 1964-1999 (Box 55, Folder 454-455)
  - Board Correspondence - Francis D. Rogers, 1966-1983 (Box 55, Folder 456)
  - Board Correspondence - Robert L. Sproull, 1979-2001 (Box 55, Folder 457)
  - Board Correspondence - Alfred R. Stern, 1980-1994 (Box 55, Folder 458)
  - Board Correspondence - Blenda J. Wilson, 1995-1999 (Box 55, Folder 459)
  - Board Correspondence - Blenda J. Wilson, 1981-1998 (Box 56, Folder 460-461)
  - Board Correspondence - Myron L. Weisfeldt, 1993-1998 (Box 56, Folder 462)
  - Karen Davis Correspondence, 1999-2000 (Box 56, Folder 463)
  - Karen Davis Correspondence 2000 (Box 56, Folder 464)
  - Karen Davis Correspondence 2000 (Box 57, Folder 465)
  - Karen Davis Correspondence 2001 (Box 57, Folder 466-468)
  - Karen Davis Correspondence 2001 (Box 58, Folder 469-470)
  - Karen Davis Correspondence 2004 (Box 58, Folder 471-473)
  - Karen Davis Correspondence 2005 (Box 59, Folder 474-476)
  - Picker Institute, 2004-2005 (Box 59, Folder 477)
  - Karen Davis Correspondence 2006 (Box 59, Folder 478)
  - Karen Davis Correspondence 2006 (Box 60, Folder 479)
  - Karen Davis Correspondence 2007 (Box 60, Folder 480)
  - Karen Davis Correspondence 2008 (Box 60, Folder 481)
  - Karen Davis Correspondence, 2009-2012 (Box 60, Folder 482)
  - Karen Davis Received Correspondence, 2006-2012 (Box 60, Folder 483)
  - Commonwealth Fund Events, 2013 (Box 60, Folder 484)
- Speeches and Presentations, 4; 7.22 Cubic Feet
  - Health Care Reform: Issues and Options, for Donna Shalala, Secretary-Designate, U.S. Department of Health and Human Services, 1992 December 20 (Box 70, Folder 625)
  - Health Care Reform: Issues and Options, 1993 January 6 (Box 70, Folder 626)
  - Health Subcommittee Retreat, 1993 January 25 (Box 70, Folder 627-628)
  - Senator Reigel, Cable-TV Show, 1994 January 5 (Box 71, Folder 629)
  - Retreat, Senior Congressional Staff, 1994 January 7 (Box 71, Folder 630)
  - The Hospital Administration Club of New York, 1994 January 10 (Box 71, Folder 631)
  - Policy Roundtable - Women's Health Policy Issues and Directions, 1994 June 14 (Box 71, Folder 632)
  - Health Care Reform in the United States, 1994 August 24 (Box 71, Folder 633)
  - ASA Meeting, Toronto, 1994 August 15-18 (Box 71, Folder 634)
  - Carnegie Corporation of New York, 1994 November 17 (Box 71, Folder 635)
  - University of Michigan, Ann Arbor, MI, 1994 November 18-19 (Box 71, Folder 636)
  - Christmas Party, 1994 December 9 (Box 71, Folder 637)
  - Remarks at NMF Annual Meeting, Dinner, Princeton, NJ, 1995 January 18 (Box 71, Folder 638-639)
  - Rosalynn Carter Reception Remarks, 1995 January 26 (Box 71, Folder 640)
  - Texas Tech Rural Health Conference, Lubbock, TX, 1995 March 24-25 (Box 71, Folder 641-642)
  - Wetherall Book Luncheon, 1995 May 25 (Box 71, Folder 643)
  - David Rogers Health Policy Colloquiuum, 1995 September 13 (Box 71, Folder 644)
  - Urban Health Institute, Keynote Address, 1995 September 15-16 (Box 71, Folder 645)
  - Managed Care Survey Planning Meeting, 1995 May 30 (Box 72, Folder 646)
  - Presentations 1995 - Miscellaneous (Box 72, Folder 647)
  - Presentations 1996 - Miscellaneous (Box 72, Folder 648-649)
  - Presentations 1996 - Miscellaneous (Box 73, Folder 650)
  - Presentations 1997 - Miscellaneous (Box 73, Folder 651)
  - Presentations 1998 - Miscellaneous (Box 73, Folder 652-653)
  - Presentations 1999 - Miscellaneous (Box 73, Folder 654)
  - Presentations 1999 - Miscellaneous (Box 74, Folder 655-656)
  - Presentations 2000, 2000 January-March (Box 74, Folder 657)
  - Presentations 2000, 2000 April-June (Box 74, Folder 658)
  - Presentations 2000, 2000 July-December (Box 74, Folder 659)
  - Presentations 2001, 2001 January-June (Box 74, Folder 660)
  - Presentations 2001, 2001 September (Box 74, Folder 661)
  - Presentations 2002 - Miscellaneous (Box 75, Folder 662)
  - Presentations 2003 - Miscellaneous (Box 75, Folder 663)
  - Presentations 2004, 2004 January-March (Box 75, Folder 664)
  - Presentations 2004, 2004 April-June (Box 75, Folder 665)
  - Presentations 2004, 2004 July-December (Box 75, Folder 666)
  - Presentations 2005, 2005 January-May (Box 75, Folder 667)
  - Presentations 2005, 2005 June-October (Box 76, Folder 668)
  - Grant Taylor Lecture, University of Texas-Houston, 2003 March 19-20 (Box 61, Folder 485)
  - Florida Policy Forum on Health Care, Orlando, FL, 2003 March 26 (Box 61, Folder 486)
  - Senate Aging Committee Testimony, Washington, D.C., 2003 March 10 (Box 61, Folder 487)
  - Alliance Medicare Panel, Washington, D. C., 2003 March 17 (Box 61, Folder 488)
  - Lubin Distinguished Professorship, New York City, 2003 April 15-16 (Box 61, Folder 489)
  - ICSBH - Opening Remarks, 2003 September 21 (Box 61, Folder 490)
  - Consumer Driven Health Care (CDHP), 2003 September 15 (Box 61, Folder 491)
  - Washington Insiders, 2004 January 25 (Box 61, Folder 492)
  - Rice Conference on Cost Effectiveness, Houston, TX, 2003 October 30 (Box 61, Folder 493)
  - Congressional Retreat, 2004 January 15-18 (Box 61, Folder 494)
  - Council on Health Care Economics-Policy, 2003 September 19 (Box 61, Folder 495)
  - Vanderbilt University, Nashville, TN, 2004 February 18 (Box 61, Folder 496)
  - Karen Davis Presentation - Handoouts, 2004 (Box 61, Folder 497)
  - Arizona Coverage and Access Now, Phoenix, AZ, 2004 March 19 (Box 62, Folder 498)
  - Task Force on the Future of Health Insurance, Washington, D. C., 2004 March 29-30 (Box 62, Folder 499)
  - Ed Brandt Symposium, Oklahoma City, OK, 2004 November 12 (Box 62, Folder 499A)
  - Pennyhill Park, 2004 July 16-18 (Box 62, Folder 500)
  - Testimony - Committee on Ways and Means, Subcommittee on Oversight, Washington, D. C., 2004 June 22 (Box 62, Folder 501)
  - Foundation Center Health Policy Panel, NY, 2004 June 22 (Box 62, Folder 502)
  - VHA Annual Strategic Planning Retreat - Keynote Speech, Phoenix, AZ, 2004 April 20 (Box 62, Folder 503)
  - Society of General Internal Medicine, Peterson Honor Lecture, Chicago, IL, 2004 May 14 (Box 62, Folder 504)
  - Insurance Deductibles, Washington, D. C., 2005 June 30 (Box 62, Folder 505)
  - Pennyhill Park, 2005 July 14-17 (Box 62, Folder 506)
  - Health Council of South Florida, FL, 2005 May 17-18 (Box 62, Folder 507)
  - FEG Meeting, Pocantico Hills, NY, 2005 May 12-13 (Box 62, Folder 508)
  - Boston Federal Reserve Bank, Annual Meeting, Cape Cod, MA, 2005 June 16-17 (Box 62, Folder 509)
  - HHS Briefing (CMMS), Washington, D. C., 2005 June 10 (Box 63, Folder 510)
  - Briefing with Senator Barack Obama, Washington, D. C., 2005 May 25 (Box 63, Folder 511)
  - XII Princeton Conference, Princeton, NJ, 2005 May 19-20 (Box 63, Folder 512)
  - Bipartisan Congressional Retreat, 2005 January 13-15 (Box 63, Folder 513)
  - College of Optometry Commencement, New York, 2005 June 5 (Box 63, Folder 514)
  - NYAM Health Services-Policy Series, NY, 2005 April 18 (Box 63, Folder 515)
  - Women at Risk: NYC Women's Health, New York City, 2005 March 8 (Box 63, Folder 516)
  - HMS Health Policy Summit, Boston, MA, 2005 September 23 (Box 63, Folder 517)
  - Rhodes Haverty Lecture, Atlanta, GA, 2005 October 27 (Box 63, Folder 518)
  - Maine Primary Care, 2005 October 5 (Box 63, Folder 519)
  - The National Quality Forum, Washington, D. C., 2005 October 6-7 (Box 63, Folder 520)
  - Princeton XIII Conference, Princeton, NJ, 2006 May 24-25 (Box 63, Folder 521)
  - ABIM Kimball Lecture, Colorado Springs, CO, 2006 July 31-August 2 (Box 64, Folder 522)
  - Health Services Research Conference, Salt Lake City, UT, 2006 February 24 (Box 64, Folder 523)
  - AHIP National Policy Forum, Washington, D. C., 2006 March 7 (Box 64, Folder 524)
  - World Congress Leadership Summit, NY, 2006 March 6-7 (Box 64, Folder 525)
  - UTMB Health Disparities Lecture Series, Galveston, TX, 2006 March 6 (Box 64, Folder 526)
  - National Association of Community Health Centers, Annual Meeting, Washington, D. C., 2006 March (Box 64, Folder 527)
  - GIH Annual Meeting, Miami, FL, 2007 February 14-16 (Box 64, Folder 528)
  - American Bar Association Annual Meeting, Orlando, FL, 2006 February 22 (Box 64, Folder 529)
  - APHA, Washington, D. C., 2007 November 7 (Box 64, Folder 530)
  - National Press Foundation Seminar, Washington, D. C., 2007 November 11 (Box 64, Folder 531)
  - Health Insurance Cost Summit, Oklahoma City, OK, 2007 November 9 (Box 65, Folder 532)
  - Australia-New Zealand Harkness Fellows Selection Committees, 2007 November 29-December 1 (Box 65, Folder 533)
  - Health Services Policy Conference, Aukland, NZ, 2007 December 2 (Box 65, Folder 534)
  - California Association of Public Hospitals, San Francisco, CA, 2007 December 6 (Box 65, Folder 535)
  - BioMed San Antonio Award, San Antonio, TX, 2007 December (Box 65, Folder 536)
  - Tosteson Health Policy Lecture, Harvard, 2007 March 15 (Box 65, Folder 537)
  - World Health Congress, Washington, D. C., 2007 April 22 (Box 65, Folder 538)
  - VHA East Coast Board Retreat, Princeton, NJ, 2007 April 26 (Box 65, Folder 539)
  - Medical Journalists Forum, Boston, MA, 2007 May 1 (Box 65, Folder 540)
  - Purdue University, West Lafayette, IN, 2007 April 23 (Box 65, Folder 541)
  - AHA Roger Larson Memorial Lecture, Washington, D. C., 2006 May 2 (Box 65, Folder 542)
  - American College of Physician Executives, Orlando, FL, 2007 May 5-10 (Box 66, Folder 543)
  - National Business Coalition on Health, Philadelphia, PA, 2007 May 16 (Box 66, Folder 544)
  - Family Voices Conference, Washington, D. C., 2007 May 24 (Box 66, Folder 545)
  - Health Care Executive Forum, New York, 2007 June 11 (Box 66, Folder 546)
  - 2007 National Medicaise Congress, Washington, D. C., 2005 June 15 (Box 66, Folder 547)
  - ISQUA International Conference, Boston, MA, 2007 September 30-October 3 (Box 66, Folder 548)
  - Flanagan Lecture, St. Louis School of Public Health, 2007 October 11 (Box 66, Folder 549)
  - Holden Public Policy Forum, Webster, St. Louis, MO, 2007 October 12 (Box 66, Folder 550)
  - Saint Alphonsus Board Retreat, Chicago, IL, 2007 June 16 (Box 66, Folder 551)
  - Catholic Health Assembly, Chicago, IL, 2007 June 19 (Box 66, Folder 552)
  - Aetna Leadership Dialogue, Hartford, CT, 2008 January 16 (Box 66, Folder 553)
  - AcademyHealth 2008 National Health Policy Conference, Washington, D. C., 2008 February 4 (Box 66, Folder 554)
  - RWJ Clinical Scholars, Yale University, 2008 February 12 (Box 66, Folder 555)
  - Baker Institute, Rice University, Houston, TX, 2008 February 26 (Box 66, Folder 556)
  - University of Pittsburgh Sonis Lecture, 2008 April 17 (Box 66, Folder 557)
  - LBJ Centennial Conference on Medicare, Austin, TX, 2008 April 28 (Box 66, Folder 558)
  - Ohio Business Roundtable - Health Policy Institute of Ohio, Columbus, OH, 2008 April 30-May 1 (Box 66, Folder 559)
  - Fred Friendly-NEJM Shattuck Lecture, Boston, MA, 2008 May 10 (Box 67, Folder 560)
  - American College of Physcians, Washington, D. C., 2008 May 15 (Box 67, Folder 561)
  - The System 2009, Minneapolis, MN, 2008 April 25-26 (Box 67, Folder 562)
  - University of Iowa, Iowa City, IA, 2008 May 5-6 (Box 67, Folder 563)
  - AUPHA Annual Meeting, Washington, D. C., 2008 June 6 (Box 67, Folder 564)
  - Harkness Fellows Leadership Series, Washington, D. C., 2008 June 9 (Box 67, Folder 565)
  - AcademyHealth Rountable, Washington, D. C., 2008 June 8 (Box 67, Folder 566)
  - AcademyHealth Annual Meeting, HSR Session, 2008 June 9 (Box 67, Folder 567)
  - Senate Finance Committee Healthcare Summit, Library of Congress, 2008 June 16 (Box 67, Folder 568)
  - Meet the Health Policy Makers, Washington, D. C., 2008 July 11 (Box 67, Folder 569)
  - House Ways and Means Committee, 2008 September 23 (Box 67, Folder 570)
  - Healthcare Financial Management Association Leadership Retreat, Washington, D. C., 2005 September 25 (Box 68, Folder 571)
  - Grantmakers in Aging-Presidents' Roundtable, Princeton, NJ, 2008 October 30 (Box 68, Folder 572)
  - Stanford University Grand Rounds, Palo Alto, CA, 2008 September 9-10 (Box 68, Folder 573)
  - Healthcare Financial Management Association, Toronto, 2008 July 25 (Box 68, Folder 574)
  - House Energy and Commerce, Subcommittee on Health Hearing, 2008 September 18 (Box 68, Folder 575)
  - American Bar Association Health Section, Washington, D. C., 2008 November 17 (Box 68, Folder 576)
  - Ed Brandt Memorial Lecture, Washington, D. C., 2008 November 18 (Box 68, Folder 577)
  - Medicare Forum, Minneapolis, 2008 November 25 (Box 68, Folder 578)
  - eHealth Initiative Annual Conference, Washington, D. C., 2008 December 4 (Box 68, Folder 579)
  - NCQA Policy Conference, Washington, D. C., 2008 December 5 (Box 69, Folder 580)
  - United Hospital Fund Conference, 2008 December 9 (Box 69, Folder 581)
  - Warburg Pincus, 2009 February 18 (Box 69, Folder 582)
  - Committee on Ways and Means Testimony, 2009 March 11 (Box 69, Folder 583)
  - Aetna Executive Forum, Washington, D. C., 2009 March 30 (Box 69, Folder 584)
  - Rep. Michael Burgess, Congressional Health Care Reform Caucus, Washington, D. C., 2009 March 30 (Box 69, Folder 585)
  - Colorado Health Foundation, Safety Net Symposium, Denver, CO, 2009 May 4 (Box 69, Folder 586)
  - ADA Jontz Memorial Panel, Washington, D. C., 2009 June 5 (Box 69, Folder 587)
  - World Bank Presentation, Washington, D. C., 2009 October 13 (Box 69, Folder 588)
  - Philanthropy New York, Health Reform Teleconference, 2009 October 15 (Box 69, Folder 589)
  - Duncan Clark Lecture, NYAM, 2010 February 22 (Box 69, Folder 590)
  - NYC Nonprofit Coordinating Committee, NY, 2010 February 25 (Box 69, Folder 591)
  - AHIP National Policy Conference, Washington, D. C., 2010 March 9 (Box 69, Folder 592)
  - Federal Reserve Detroit Regional Chamber Annual Meeting, 2010 April 26 (Box 69, Folder 593)
  - SGIM Annual Meeting, Minneapolis, MN, 2010 April 30 (Box 69, Folder 594)
  - Maryland Hospital Association Annual Meeting, Baltimore, 2010 June 4 (Box 69, Folder 595)
  - ILC Age Boom Academy, New York City, 2010 June 9 (Box 69, Folder 596)
  - Ohio State University Health Services Management and Policy Alumni Society, Columbus, OH, 2010 October 22 (Box 69, Folder 597)
  - Stony Brook University Health Reform Symposium, 2010 November 1 (Box 69, Folder 598)
  - NYU Payment Reform Panel, 2010 November 10 (Box 70, Folder 599)
  - Foundation for Community Health and Salisbury Forum, Salisbury, CT, 2011 May 13 (Box 70, Folder 600)
  - RWJ Clinical Scholars, Yale Medical School, 2011 September 22 (Box 70, Folder 601)
  - Karen Davis Miscellaneous Articles - Presentations, 1972-1992 (Box 70, Folder 602)
  - ABIM Foundation, Rancho Palos, Verdes, CA, 2012 July 28-31 (Box 70, Folder 603)
  - University of Michigan Legacy of the War on Poverty Conference, Ann Arbor, MI, 2012 June 13 (Box 70, Folder 604)
  - Academic Medicine Conference, Johns Hopkins University, Baltimore, 2012 June 11 (Box 70, Folder 605)
  - Alliance for Health Reform Briefing - Rising Costs of Health Care, Washington, D. C., 2012 June 12 (Box 70, Folder 606)
  - AcademyHealth ARM, Orlando, FL, 2012 June 24-26 (Box 70, Folder 607)
  - ADA Jontz Lecture, Washington, D. C., 2012 September 13 (Box 70, Folder 608)
  - Democratic Caucus Retreat, Cambridge, MD, 2012 January 26 (Box 70, Folder 609)
  - Harvard Tosteson Lecture, Boston, MA, 2012 February 17 (Box 70, Folder 610)
  - ProMedica Community Health Forum, Toledo, OH, 2012 February 21 (Box 70, Folder 611)
  - GIH Annual Meeting, Baltimore, MD, 2012 March 7 (Box 70, Folder 612)
  - National Medical Fellowships, Champions of Health Awards Gala, Union League Club, 2012 April 17 (Box 70, Folder 613)
  - ProMedica Board of Directors, Toledo, OH, 2012 April 24 (Box 70, Folder 614)
  - FEG Meeting, Washington, D. C., 2012 May 20-22 (Box 70, Folder 615)
  - Century Foundation ACA Panel, New York City, 2012 July 11 (Box 70, Folder 616)
  - Toledo Rotary Club, Toledo, OH, 2012 September 17 (Box 70, Folder 617)
  - Geisinger Board of Directors, Danville, PA, 2012 September 19-20 (Box 70, Folder 618)
  - United Hospital Fund Gala, Health Care Leadership Award, New York City, 2012 October 1 (Box 70, Folder 619)
  - Cosmos Club Health Group, Washington, D. C., 2012 October 8 (Box 70, Folder 620)
  - IOM Annual Meeting, Health Policy Interest Group Panel, Washington, D. C., 2012 October 14 (Box 70, Folder 621)
  - IOM Annual Meeting, Health Care in 2020 Panel, Washington, D. C., 2012 October 15 (Box 70, Folder 622)
  - HCEF, New York City, 2012 October 24 (Box 70, Folder 623)
  - New York Academy of Medicine, Medal for Distinguished Contribution to Health Policy, 2012 November 8 (Box 70, Folder 624)
  - Karen Davis Speeches/Presentations, 2005 January-February (Box 159, Folder 1200)
  - Health Care Financial Management Association, Phoenix, AZ (Box 159, Folder 1201)
  - Boston - Long Term Care Colloquium, 2005 June 25 (Box 159, Folder 1202)
  - Medicare at 40, 2005 June 26 (Box 159, Folder 1203)
  - Group Health Roundtable, 2005 October 13 (Box 159, Folder 1204)
  - Karen Davis Presentations, 2005 October-November (Box 160, Folder 1205)
  - Karen Davis Presentations, 2006 January-June (Box 160, Folder 1206-1207)
  - Center on Philanthropy at Indiana University, Indianapolis, IN, 2006 August 24-25 (Box 160, Folder 1208)
  - National Consumer Driven Healthcare Summit, Washington, D. C., 2006 September 14 (Box 160, Folder 1209)
  - West Virginia Hospital Association - Annual Meeting, 2006 September 27-29 (Box 160, Folder 1210)
  - Danish Regions Conference, Copenhagen, Denmark, 2006 October 10 (Box 160, Folder 1211)
  - National Academy for State Health Policy - Annual Policy Conference, Pittsburgh, PA, 2006 October 15-17 (Box 161, Folder 1212)
  - Picker Award - ISQuA Annual Meeting, London, 2006 October 24-25 (Box 161, Folder 1213)
  - Columbia University Executive MPH Graduation, 2006 November 3 (Box 161, Folder 1214)
  - Wisconsin Collaborative for Health Care Quality, Madison, WI, 2006 November 9 (Box 161, Folder 1215)
  - Levinger Lecture, Brown University, 2006 November 28 (Box 161, Folder 1216)
  - Brookings Forum, Washington, D.C., 2006 December 15 (Box 161, Folder 1217)
  - Cornell Roundtable on the Uninsured, 2007 January 18 (Box 161, Folder 1218)
  - Charlene Rydell Lecture, Augusta, ME, 2007 January 26 (Box 161, Folder 1219)
  - CareGroup Board of Directors, Boston, 2007 February 1 (Box 161, Folder 1220)
  - New York Times - Markle Foundation Journalism Institute, New York City, 2007 February 6 (Box 161, Folder 1221)
  - Henry Ford Hospital Grand Rounds, Detroit, MI, 2007 February 8 (Box 161, Folder 1222)
  - AARP Board of Directors, Washington, D.C., 2007 February 13 (Box 161, Folder 1223)
- Meetings and Program Files, 5; 34.16 Cubic Feet
  - Commonwealth Fund Conference and Workshop Manual, 1984 March (Box 76, Folder 669)
  - Commonwealth Fund Slide Collection, 1984 (Box 76, Folder 670)
  - Board of Directors - Program Plan Meeting, 1988 February 9 (Box 76, Folder 671)
  - Program Staff Policy and Practices, 1987-1988 (Box 76, Folder 672)
  - Health Security Plan (Box 76, Folder 673)
  - Grant Lists - Completed, In Progress, Active, 1991 (Box 76, Folder 674)
  - Completed Grant Reports, 1985-1988 (Box 77, Folder 675-676)
  - Commonwealth Fund Nominating Committee Meeting, 1993 May 25 (Box 77, Folder 677)
  - Health Care Reform Program Advisory Committee Meeting, 1994 October 21 (Box 77, Folder 678)
  - Young African-American Men Survey, 1994 (Box 77, Folder 679)
  - Health Care Coverage and Quality Program Advisory Committee Meeting, 1995 October 20 (Box 78, Folder 680)
  - Fostering the Independence of Frail Elders, 1994 (Box 78, Folder 681)
  - Families and Work Institute, 1994 (Box 78, Folder 682)
  - CERP - Five Nation Elderly Survey, 1991 (Box 78, Folder 683)
  - AARP CEPLA Advisory Committee Meeting (Box 78, Folder 684)
  - Commission on Elderly People Living Alone (CEPLA) - Final Meeting-Dinner, 1991 November 6 (Box 78, Folder 685)
  - CEPLA-AARP Media Briefing, 1992 November 19 (Box 78, Folder 686)
  - Margaret E. Mahoney - Karen Davis Meeting Notes, 1992 (Box 78, Folder 687)
  - Margaret E. Mahoney - Karen Davis Meeting Notes, 1993 (Box 79, Folder 688)
  - Project BEGIN, 1994 (Box 79, Folder 689)
  - CONSAD Research Corp. Report on Jobs At Risk, 1991 September (Box 79, Folder 690)
  - Community Care Network Meeting, 1994 April (Box 79, Folder 691)
  - Dr. Ros Hirschowitz, 1994 (Box 79, Folder 692)
  - Harvard Medical School Department of Health Care Policy, 1992 (Box 79, Folder 693)
  - Miscellaneous Meetings, 1993-1995 (Box 79, Folder 694)
  - Senior Program Staff Meetings, 1992 February-1993 June (Box 79, Folder 695-696)
  - Commission on Behavioral and Social Sciences and Education, 1993-1994 (Box 80, Folder 697-698)
  - Center for National Policy, 1992 (Box 80, Folder 699)
  - Agency for Health Care Policy and Research, 1994 December 19 (Box 80, Folder 700)
  - Paul Beeson Physician Scholars in Aging Research Program, 1995 (Box 80, Folder 701)
  - Paul Beeson Physician Scholars in Aging Research Program, 1994 (Box 80, Folder 702)
  - Paul Beeson Physician Scholars in Aging Research Program, 1994 (Box 81, Folder 703)
  - School to Career Network, 1994-1995 (Box 81, Folder 704)
  - Joint National Health Care Policy, 1992 December (Box 81, Folder 705)
  - Hospital Youth Mentoring, 1995 March 3 (Box 81, Folder 705A)
  - French-American Foundation Delegation on Maternal and Child Health Care, 1992-1995 (Box 81, Folder 706)
  - Academic Health Centers - Blumenthal-Meyer Report, 1995 (Box 81, Folder 707)